<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Boni's Projects - Projects</title><link href="https://bonioloff.github.io/" rel="alternate"></link><link href="https://bonioloff.github.io/feeds/projects.atom.xml" rel="self"></link><id>https://bonioloff.github.io/</id><updated>2021-04-28T10:20:00-05:00</updated><subtitle>Boni's Projects</subtitle><entry><title>Financial Inclusion and Economic Development</title><link href="https://bonioloff.github.io/financial-inclusion-economic-development.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2021-04-28T10:20:00-05:00</published><updated>2021-04-28T10:20:00-05:00</updated><author><name>Boni Oloff</name></author><id>tag:bonioloff.github.io,2021-04-28:/financial-inclusion-economic-development.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;An exploratory study to learn how micro aspects of financial inclusion play an important role in improving welfare.&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;This is a project of me (@bonioloff) and Harry Satriyo Hendharto (@harryhendharto) for the Data and Programming for Public Policy II - PPHA 30536 class at The University of Chicago.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In this project, we explored the 2017 World Bank Global Financial Inclusion (Findex) database as the latest publicly available cross-countries consumer survey data about the access of basic financial service (demand-side) in order to understand the role of financial inclusion for economic development. Example of key measures from Global Findex are the % of bank account ownership and reasons why people do not have a bank account. We also combined those with 2017 IMF Financial Access Survey (FAS) database to balance the information from the financial service provider perspective (supply-side). Example of key measures from FAS are the number of ATM machines and the number of bank branches in a country. The objective of this analysis is to provide policy maker with stronger rationale to design more specific intervention rather than a generic one. For example, which one should be prioritized to improve overall welfare, a free bank account for poor people or increasing the presence of bank branches network.&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="Projects"></category><category term="School"></category></entry></feed>